# Maho Morinaga

<u>tr27e1104@gmail.com</u> | (604) 349 9484 | <u>https://maho-morinaga.netlify.app/</u> | <u>https://github.com/MahoMori</u> | <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/maho-morinaga/</u>

## **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Seeking to be a full stack developer with polyglot skills. Currently a student in Vancouver studying web application development. Having started walking the tech path last year, I am very ambitious and passionate about coding. Diligent and hardworking, I am eager to learn new skills and help the company and my coworkers achieve their goals.

# **SKILLS**

LanguagesHTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, GraphQL, Node.jsFrameworks and LibrariesReact.js/Redux, Material UI, styled-components, ExpressSystems and DatabasesGit/GitHub, MongoDB/Mongoose, Firebase, MySQLOtherAgile, Figma, Illustrator, Photoshop, Microsoft Office

## **DEVELOPMENT EXPERIENCE**

OpenTree EducationVancouver, CanadaOpen Source DeveloperMay 2022 - June 2022

Worked on a community dev team for an open source project for OpenTree Education. Created a user profile feature for a students management system.

Tasks completed include: Agile, onboarding, pair programming, GitHub collaboration, work in a team, a full project cycle.

#### **PROJECTS**

<u>Creative Product Generator</u> (React.js, Redux toolkit, TypeScript, styled components)

May, 2022

The web application that uses OpenAI API. When the users input product description, it generates product ad and name.

<u>Vancouver Hot Chocolate Adventure</u> (React.js, Redux toolkit, TypeScript, styled components)

Mar, 2022

Using Geolocation API, this web application compares user's location and a shop location to check as "Been To".

Grocery Budget Calculator (React.js, Redux toolkit, TypeScript, styled components)

Mar, 2022

The web application that keeps track of budget for grocery shopping.

Space Gallery (React.js, styled components)

Jan, 2022

The image gallery that users can like and unlike pictures using NASA API.

To go/To do List (React.js, Redux toolkit, Material UI)

Dec, 2021

The website that users can add, edit and delete lists of places to go and things to do.

<u>Light Night Lamp</u> (HTML, CSS)

Aug, 2021

The ecommerce landing page design for the store selling lamps.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Gakuhou-sha Aichi, Japan

Editorial Assistant September 2020 - March 2021

- Read through and corrected numerous spelling and grammar mistakes in drafts for English workbooks.
- Not only pointed out these mistakes and unnatural use of English, but also suggested alternatives.

KSG Dublin, Ireland

Catering Assistant November 2019 - August 2020

• Served customers at a sandwich bar with a welcoming attitude, and was always thinking what should be done next to make the waiting time as short as possible.

Besttech Co., Ltd. Aichi, Japan

Editor/Translator April 2017 - July 2019

• Translated and edited fighter airplane manuals using MS Word, Illustrator and Photoshop.

#### **EDUCATION**

**CICCC - Cornerstone International Community College of Canada** 

May 2021 – present (until Apr 2023)

Web and Mobile Application Development | Diploma